Thank you for watching!
Stay happy everyone!
Hello! This time I'll be talking with Nomizuho from Tsubaki Factory and Fuka Doi from Tsubaki Factory.
This time, we're going to be sharing with you two, so please bear with us until the end.
Fuka Doi is making her first appearance as an MC on “Halo! So, let's start by introducing ourselves.
So please start by introducing yourself.
I'm Fuka Doi, a new member of Tsubaki Factory.
I'm 14 years old, a junior high school student, from Osaka.
My hobby is reading manga.
My special skills are Soranbushi and Go.
My idol is Ms. Ono.
He's so cute!
I'm so happy!
I'd like to delve into this right now.
I'm a little curious about her special skills.
I'd like to hear about them.
You're good at Soran Bushi and Go, right?
Yes.
How did you get the Soranbushi?
I was a dance leader, and there was a dance leader, and I became a dance leader, and I became a dance leader, and I became a dance leader, and I became a dance leader, and I became a dance leader, and I became a dance leader.
I was a dance leader, and I've seen your Soranbushi, and it was really cool, so I'd like you to see it someday.
Another skill is Go.
Yes, sir.
When I was in the first grade of elementary school, there was a Go club at school, and I joined it and started playing Go, and I fell in love with it.
So you've been playing Go for about 8 or 9 years?
About nine years? That's a long time.
And at the end, when you looked at me and said Ono-san, as a senior whom you admire, I thought it was very cute.
It's written here, so I'll ask you.
It says what attracts you to me.
I like your smile, the way you smile every day.
Thank you, that makes me happy.
I love your smile, too.
I also love your smile. I know you've only been with Tsubaki Factory for a short time...
I want you to spend your time freely at Tsubaki Factory without worrying about such things.
I'm really looking forward to seeing your smiling face next to mine.
Thank you very much.
Now, please take a look at this video.
Please take a look. Please come in.
The Yokohama Arena concert is a very important one for us as Angstrom.
I hope the performance will be the culmination of the current 11 members' performance in many aspects.
I will do my best for every second of the show.
I'll do my best every single second.
It's really terrible.
Thank you very much.
Let's do our best.
I'll do my best.
He's so cute!
He's so cute today. He's got a big forehead.
Oh!
That's not true.
It's quite rare. I'm very lucky.
I'm lucky. I'll do my best.
I'll do my best.
Hello! Hello! Station
Hello! Station
Wait, wait. It's starting?
It's starting.
You finally felt it just now, didn't you?
Really.
We both high-fived each other, almost shedding tears.
I don't know how many times we high-fived.
Let's do our best. We were talking about the meaning of life.
I think we did it four or five times. I'll do my best, but...
I'm not in the mood for it.
It's going to be fun.
Good luck with the opening.
Yes, everyone.
I have such an important day.
I'm that size.
Thank you very much.
I see that you're the one calling me.
Come on, come on, come on. Come on, come on, come on.
I'm nervous
I'm nervous.
Okay, I'm nervous.
Wow, it's going to show, oh no.
Everyone is greedy.
I think you should enjoy yourselves.
Let's show the culmination at 11:00!
Yes, sir!
Okay, here we go!
Yes!
Here we go!
Yeah!
Squid! The bite! Chew! Reina! Kero! For! Hakanya! Pei! Pyunpyun! Kanana! Kipuya! Swai!
All right! All right! Bon appétit!
Yes!
Very good! Try it!
Aye! Ai! Ai! Ai! Ai! Ai! Ai!
No one measured the difference in width.
But they'll never know.
After he's dead, his reputation grows.
It's a pattern of retconning.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
That's not what I'd call a meteoric rise.
I'm just saying, you've got to take a chance.
I have to prove it now.
Late bloomer.
That's your life now.
Turn it upside down.
I want to grab it now
Late blooming
I've had it with these times
That's why my time's up
I want it now
Anything Nothing.
Don't let it fool you.
No matter what the times
And never be carried away
A life of great promise
No more of this life
Turn it upside down
I want to grab it now
It's not that kind of life anymore
That's the life I'm living
That's why my time is up
I want to go through now
I want to be a great person until I'm a late bloomer
Late bloomer, late bloomer
Late bloomer, late bloomer, late bloomer
Big time, big time, big time
Ready!
Great performance, great performance, great performance, great performance...
More and more!
Great job, great job, great job, great job, great job, great job
Thanks for your work!
This is Mizuho Ono of Tsubaki Factory and
Fuka Doi of Tsubaki Factory.
I'd like to talk a little bit about each other from here.
I'm going to ask you some questions.
So let's answer them in a quick tempo without thinking too much.
Yes, sir.
Here we go.
What is your favorite school event?
The school festival.
What would you say is Doi Fuuka's instruction manual?
Laughs a lot, sleeps a lot.
I like to touch my elbows. Spring tour is over! What did you notice after the tour?
It was a lot of fun. I realized that I need to build up my physical strength more and more.
Where is your favorite place in Osaka? Universal Studios Japan.
What kind of idol do you want to be?
I want to be an idol who can bring smiles, energy, and power to people. I want to be an idol who can bring smiles, energy, and power to people!
First of all, what is your favorite school event?
What did I say?
The school festival.
The school festival!
Why the school festival?
I'm in the dance club.
We had the opportunity to present our work at the festival.
So I like festivals.
So you like being in front of people?
That's a little bit...
It makes me nervous.
I'm nervous, but everyone is.
And what's your favorite place in Osaka?
Universal Studios Japan.
I highly recommend it!
What's the best part?
It's so much fun!
With friends and family
I've been saying that for a long time.
Is that right?
Yes, I do.
I love that it's a place you can go over and over again and never get tired of it.
I've been to Universal Studio Japan twice.
I hope to go there with Koka-chan someday.
Questions for Ms. Ono will be asked after the VTR.
Hello! STE!
This video was created by a viewer
Thank you for watching!
Angulum Bilitar Ichigeki Now on SAIO
Angulum Rumors of Narcissi
Now on sale
Angulum, Thank you, Hello, Goodbye, Now on sale!
Angulum Concert 2024 Secret Secret Sasaki Rikako Final
Come to the world of love, you, too, is over!
I finally finished the voice around my face, but...
What was it? What was that?
First of all, the setlist was so cool, it was just outrageous.
I think it was a lot of fun, and I could enjoy various genres of angsty music as well as cute ones,
It went by so fast.
I feel like I say this every time, but it was really fast, but it was a lot of fun.
It was a lot of fun, wasn't it?
It was a lot of fun.
Thank you very much.
See you later.
Let's see what you got, Kero-chan.
Kero-chan.
Yes, really.
The yellow penlights were so beautiful, and I felt sad that Ms. Sasaki was graduating,
I felt sad that Ms. Sasaki was going to graduate, but I also felt that it had been difficult for the 11 of us to perform together as a complete unit,
I was very happy to be able to perform on this big stage with all 11 of us.
Sixth place went to Momi.
Yes, it was.
Yes, that's right. It all happened so fast. It was so fast.
We were playing various songs, and I knew that Ms. Sasaki had been with us since the beginning of Angstrom.
We had spent a lot of time together, so I sang some of the songs remembering that,
It was the second time for me to be in the side as Ange,
I felt like... I have to work harder.
I felt that I had to work harder, and since Ms. Sasaki left behind a huge legacy of 10 years after her graduation, I wanted to do my best to make up for it, little by little, with everyone's help.
I'm okay with that.
How was it for you, Mr. Sasaki?
I was really tired of crying.
As I said on stage, the place where my emotions come out the most is the stage.
As I said on stage, the place where my emotions come out the most is the stage, and I really felt that I had a day where I laughed a lot and cried a lot today,
If I had to sum it up in one word, I would say I had a lot of fun.
If I had to sum it up in one word, I would say it was a lot of fun.
I put a lot of my passion into this concert, so I hope you really enjoyed it,
I hope you really enjoyed it,
I hope you really enjoyed it, and I was very happy to see such a wonderful live performance at the end.
Thank you very much.
Best regards. Best regards
Hallo! Ste.
Next, I would like to ask you a question, Mr. Ono!
Shanghai concert in May Please tell us about your memories in Shanghai.
I was so happy to be welcomed at the airport.
What is the goal of Tsubaki Factory now that you have a new organization?
We want to be a group that can do anything, not just be an idol group.
I want to be a group that can do anything.
What do you want to keep in mind as a new sub-leader?
To be full of eyes.
What do you want in summer?
Goods that make me feel cooler
We are going to release a new single on August 28th.
Please tell us about the charm of the new song ahead of time.
Mature, refreshing, fun
What do you want to keep in mind as a new sub-leader?
What I want to keep in mind as a new sub-leader
I was told to put on a lot of eyes.
I often borrowed this from Runo's words.
I was very happy and impressed when she told me I had lots of eyes.
I was very happy and it made a big impression on me.
Various things...
I want to be a person who can notice things.
I want to be a person who can notice various things, so I'm going to do my best to notice everyone's details with my full attention.
It's been about a week since we started our new organization, so our goal for Tsubaki Factory is to become a group that goes beyond the framework of idols.
Tsubaki Factory is going to have a regular TV show called “Go Ze Tsubaki Factory”.
We have a regular TV show called “Goze Tsubaki Factory”, so we want to keep our idol-like character, but at the same time, we want to challenge everything with all our might.
We also want to be a group that can sing idol-like songs as well as cool and exciting songs that don't sound like idols.
We also want to be a group that can sing cool and exciting songs that aren't idol-like.
Let's be together!
Let's be together! We'll continue after this.
I want to be without it. I should be more proper.
I want to be without it. No, I should be better than this.
It's as if I have two hearts in one body.
It's as if it's two.
Deep in my closed chest...
Don't fight each other any more
The mirror that wakes me up with a dizzying alarm Jittery wake-up mirror
Tickle my heavy eyes
To us on a dazzling red day
Everyone smiles in their hearts
with a connected face
Running now to live
I'm sure we're all in pain
You're not the only one
I'm sure it's the same for all of us
You're not the only one.
Just be yourself, be mindful, be at ease.
I'll make the best of it.
I'm weak and I'm strong
The one who gently accepts me
Just for a nod of the head
I'm ashamed of my lightened load
It's nothing to be ashamed of.
To say it's hard when it's hard
Still sinking like a cage deep in this chest
Sinking like a cage
Feelings I don't even know the name of
I wonder if I'll meet them in order to grow up
If I ever meet them
I wonder if I'll be able to say it properly
I'm sure we're all fools.
You're not the only one
I'm sure we're all the same
Ginny, Ginny, the alarm bell rings
To a present you've never seen before
I'm taking everyone with me as I run out
I still miss my first time
I want to see the joy
I'm running with you on the road that leads to the road that leads to the road that leads to the road that leads to the road
I'm watching you I'm watching.
I'm sure we're all in pain.
You're not the only one.
I'm sure we're all the same.
Maybe you're just as stupid as everyone else.
You're not the only one.
You're not the only one
I delete explanations
You're not the only one.
You're not the only one
It's not just you
I'm sure we're all the same
It's not just you, it's not just you Dance
Subtitle Kiminomiya
As of today, June 19th
I, Rikako Sasaki, will graduate from Hello Project and I love you, I won't stop loving you, Angelem.
Thank you very much.
I was born and raised in Kesennuma.
I was an energetic girl who was always running around and didn't know what to be afraid of.
I was the happiest person in my heart.
was the happiest thing in my heart.
It only takes a moment for it to fall apart
There is no such thing as normal
The first emotion that sprouted in my young heart
It was the first turning point in my life
It was the turning point in my life.
March 11 is and will always be
I will never forget it.
I will never forget how a smile
how much a smile can illuminate and embrace you.
It is precisely because the light has gone out that I want to be a light for others.
I want to be a light for others
With such a strong desire
I started my life as an idol.
The first goal that I could achieve One of the first goals I made.
To be a member of Hello Project
It was the first big light and dream born in my small heart.
I jumped into the world for the first time without knowing what was right or left
No matter what I saw, it shone brightly for me.
There were times when I wanted to stop and turn around
Of course, it wasn't all fun and games
I knew that, but
I suddenly looked up from looking down and looked around me
I saw friends who reached out to me
and those who strengthened me.
Someday I would like to grow up in this place
I want to nurture the existence of Rikako Sasaki in this place.
I have come to believe so strongly.
From 2014 to 2024
I have been a member of ANGELUM for about 10 years
I am creating the work of Rikako Sasaki.
The person who helped me to enjoy my youth and establish who I am
It's undeniably because of the irreplaceable existence of Angelem that I have been able to enjoy my youth and establish who I am as a person.
I can't put it into words.
It would be a waste to put it all into words.
I feel that it would be a waste to put it all into words.
I think it would be a waste to put it all into words.
What is love to me?
Love is so free, so difficult, so tortuous, and so painful that it sometimes brings tears to my eyes.
They are the friends who taught me that love is so free, so difficult, so tortuous, and sometimes so painful that it brings tears to my eyes.
They are the ones who taught me how delicate the life of the heart is
They have taught me how sensitive the heart is to life.
Before being members, we are all human beings.
Sometimes it is difficult to live like a human being
I love the human side of you all.
I have you all in my daily life now
Hanana!
Where are you, Hanana?
There you are!
Yup!
Yup, over here! Yup, over here.
Yes, sir.
Yuki-chan
Yuki-chan.
Baka-nyan
Yes
Shion
Yes, sir.
Vomit
Feeling like eating
Rin
Yes
Rera
chew
Yes
chewing
yes
Sue.
Sooo...
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
When I think that tomorrow will be a different world
Sometimes it's hard to keep moving forward
Although I made my own choice
I still love you all so much
I don't know if I'll be able to hold myself together
I don't know if I can keep myself together
That's how tight I want to hold on in my life
It's a warmth I want to keep until my life is over
We share so many feelings, words, time and space
The time that we have spent together, hand in hand, moving forward step by step
All of them are shining so brightly
Even small happiness feels like big happiness
Walking with everyone, sometimes bumping into each other
I love the time we've spent together, sometimes bumping into each other and laughing at each other.
Thank you for meeting me Thank you for meeting me.
Thank you for all the cuddles.
Thank you for joking around and laughing with me about silly things.
You've been straight and honest with me
Thank you so much for running with me all the way here.
I will continue to love you in the past and in the future in whatever form
It's the present that creates the future
Be the best and the strongest you can be
Please make up the future of Angulum with your own colors.
And to my fans
The timing of our encounters is different for everyone.
Some of you have known me for a long time
Some of you have known me for a long time, and some of you wish you could have met me sooner.
But I'm happy to live in this time when you and I met
I am happy to live in the time when you and I met.
I am happy to live as one of your lights
I am truly happy to live as one of your lights.
Thank you very much for watching.
It is because of all of you who have always accepted me with great love no matter what
I am able to exist as I am now because of all of you who have always accepted me with great love no matter what.
Love is nothing but heavy
Because I live my life with that in mind
With the overflowing love from all of you
The time you spent looking at me straight in the eye
It has been and will continue to be a reason for me to have confidence and love myself
It has been and will be my support and encouragement
And I believe it will lead to happiness and smiles.
As you always wish for my happiness
I wish for everyone's happiness more than anyone else
I am the sun that shines on you all
I am the sunflower that shines on you all
I believe that I am a sunflower that can live only because of your light.
I think of myself as a sunflower that lives because of your light.
and the fans.
I wish you all happiness.
I felt as if we were all supporting each other in some way.
Thank you for sharing your hearts with me regardless of our positions.
If I may say one selfish thing If I may say one selfish thing
Please let me continue to be your sun
And let me live as a sunflower
When you are living, there will be nights when you are bitter and sad
And there are days when you want to stop moving forward
At that time, please look around you
For you have given me great warmth and love
There must be so many people around you
There must be a lot of people around you who are willing to reach out to you.
You are never alone.
Please keep smiling
Life is a series of choices
I know there is fear of what lies ahead.
But I hope that I can turn that fear into excitement.
I'm going to hit it and crush it, and even if it doesn't work, I'm going to get up again and take it one step at a time.
I will make the most of my one and only life.
I will become the top idol in the universe!
To the person I was back then when I said that and ran away from my hometown Kesennuma
Now my daily life is full of smiles.
I'm standing on the stage of Yokohama Arena.
It's unbelievable, isn't it?
Everything in the past is the precious time that made me what I am today.
For the past 11 years, I've been running forward with a big dream
I have no regrets about my choices.
To everyone who has met Rikako Sasaki of Angelem
To all of you who have loved me
I thank you from the bottom of my heart.
And I love you from the bottom of my heart.
From tomorrow, I will start my life not as Rikako Sasaki of Angulum
I will start my life as a new Rikako Sasaki.
Embracing warmth, gratitude and love like treasures
I will live my life loving myself and those around me
Thank you for creating a world of love with me today.
See you all again!
I hope that the environment surrounding all of you, whom I love so much, will be a kind world.
May it be a world of kindness.
June 19, 2024
Everyone's Sunshine Angstrom Rikako Sasaki The Sunshine for Everyone Angulum Rikako Sasaki
Beyond
Seino
Let's go beyond
Beyond
Mizunami Ono of Tsubaki Factory and
Fuka Yutaka of Tsubaki Factory.
We'd like to get to know more about Fuka-chan, so we'd like to dig a little deeper
I'd like to dig a little deeper.
At the Hello Project concert in the winter, she introduced herself
I introduced my favorite things at each concert.
This time, I asked them to write down as many of their favorite things as they could think of in their sketchbooks.
I'd like to have her share it with us.
Here we go!
There you go!
A lot of things!
Tomato swing
I'm curious about some of them.
May I dig deeper into the ones I'm interested in?
Yes, ma'am.
Let's start with tomatoes.
My favorite food is tomatoes.
I wrote tomatoes.
What kind of tomatoes do you like?
I like a fistful of tomatoes.
That's right.
A fistful of tomatoes.
Sweet tomatoes.
No, not sweet tomatoes. I like them. It's tomato season from now on.
I'll eat a lot of tomatoes.
I'm interested in all of them, but I'm really curious about the A and the A3, the two A's.
A? A is my favorite letter of the alphabet.
I like A in ABC. Why do you like A in A?
A is my favorite because it's the first letter in the alphabet and it stands out the most.
Then what's your favorite hiragana?
My favorite first letter is E.
Oh, you don't like A? Oh, you don't mean “A”?
I'm curious. Can I ask you something? Why E?
I like E because it's easy to write.
Oh, that's what I thought! It's the first one, so it's not so easy.
What about A?
My favorite hair size. I thought it was the name of the exit of some train station.
You like Mr. A? I like Mr. A. So you like big hair? Yes, I do.
Why? There's a video of her dancing, and she puts her hair on a T-shirt.
I like Mr. A because his hair was Mr. A.
Hello! Ste.
Then this frying pan.
The frying pan is my favorite cooking utensil.
Do you cook?
Sometimes I cook for myself.
What do you cook?
I cook fried rice.
At 3:00 p.m.?
It's my favorite time of day.
Your favorite time of day?
Because it's easy to see.
Easy to watch? Not during snack time or something.
Yes, sir.
When you look at it as a clock? I like 15:00 because it's the easiest to read on a clock.
77?
What's with the 7? I like two numbers... because it makes me feel lucky.
I'm sure you're getting to know Yuka better too.
Let's say hello again.
May I say hello to everyone from 5 years ago?
I'm going to work even harder so that you can get to know me better and better.
This is Haloste, a show by Mizuho Ono and Fuka Doi of Tsubaki Factory.
It's time to say goodbye.
This was your first time to MC Haloste, how was it?
I was really nervous, but Ms. Ono was so kind that I was able to relax.
Relaxed? I'm glad.
I was so happy to be able to be a part of your first time.
Here's an announcement.
It will be the first single for the three new members, so I hope everyone will enjoy watching the new Tsubaki Factory. We will be releasing a new single on August 28th, and it will be the first single for the three new members, so I hope everyone will enjoy watching the current Tsubaki Factory.
We will be performing at Spark 2024 in Kawasaki from April 13th to 15th. We three new members will be working hard in our lessons for the event.
We will be uploading new videos every Wednesday, so be sure to give us a high rating and subscribe to our channel!
This time we have Mizuho Ono and Chicken Foo from Tsubaki Factory!
Farewell.
The answer you've been looking for, the dream you've been longing for...
The moment I got it, something just popped
I thought I knew this day would come one day
Goodbye, that echo, I can't chew it anymore
Brittle as glass, our hearts are still connected.
I think of all the times we believed in each other.
I'm so proud, so proud, so proud
We looked up at the same sky, we shared the same wind.
We've shared our smiles
And now there's a light shining on each of our paths
It's time for us to go, Tears on your face
I'll wave to you, I'll wave to you, I'll wave to you, I'll wave to you
Thank you I love you, bye
Every time I know that I don't have anything
I'm afraid of what the future holds for you
When I didn't try and accept it all
You wanted to be with me
I've always known you
I know you.
You've always reached out to me
You showed me that I'm not alone
Though there's so much I haven't told you
I'll hold them close to my heart
I'll start walking without looking back
I'll tell you that at the time of Corona, there was nothing
I'd be lying if I said I didn't understand
I'd be lying.
I love the days that have gone by too much
No matter how much time goes by
Will never fade away.
And all that we've built will never be forgotten And don't forget everything you've learned.
Always.
Thank you and all goodbyes
Wow, I'm only looking forward
I've been running and I've kept on running and I've kept on running
I've always had your warmth by my side
Because I had your warmth by my side
Even in my heart
저희's sentencehall stopped
When it snows and rains and is cold
We've shared so much
I'd be lying if I said I had no regrets
I'd be lying
The days that have gone by
Too much to see
Each one of our paths
There's a light shining through
It's time for us to start our journey
Tears don't suit me
I'll wave to you
Thank you, Hello, Goodbye
Forever
From the bottom of my heart
Thank you, Hello, Goodbye
I love you
One MC at a time, I wanted to speak one at a time!
I've been holding back, for a long time!
Thank you! Thank you!
Thank you!
You're so lucky!
Thank you! Thank you! Thank you! Thank you!
What's this? What's this?
Oh, it's a secret!
No! It's a secret message!
I wanted you to put a heart in there.
Thank you.
That's great. That's great.
You're amazing.
That's beautiful.
That's great.
Give me that strength.
Good job, everyone.
You were so cute.
Cheese.
Okay, thank you.
All right.
I have to go.
He's so cute.
It's my baby.
It's parented by an angel.
What do you want?
Love.
Oh, I thought I was burned.
It's been a short year, really.
I'm having a baby.
There's a baby. Where is it?
There's a baby. Where's the baby?
There's a baby. I'm having a baby.
Me too.
I, Rikako Sasaki, have graduated from ANGELUM and HALO! Project.
Thank you very much.
I really joined the Halo! Project when I was 11 years old when I joined.
I was really skinny.
I really jumped into the world of Halo! Project when I was in the 6th or 5th grade,
I was really, really determined,
I think I really ran through the world of Halo!
Even now that I've graduated, I still feel as if I'm not a member of Hello!
I still feel as if I am no longer a member of Hello Project,
I can't believe that I am no longer a member of Hello Project,
But I am so grateful to all the people who helped me to come to this wonderful end,
I am truly grateful to all the people who made it possible for me to come to such a wonderful end.
Thank you very much.
I hope that you will continue to support us as well as Angeleum,
If you have time, I would be very happy if you could take a good look at me, too.
I would be happy if you could take a good look at me. But most of all, please look at Angulum.
So thank you all very much. This is Sasaki Rikagakubu. Bye bye. See you soon.